嘿,罗斯
Hey, Ross.
真高兴有人在这里 你可以帮我把拉链拉起来吗?
I'm so gIad someone's here. CouId you zip me up?
-当然可以 -谢谢
-Sure. -Thank you.
你相信从我家到这里的路上…
Can you beIieve no one between my apartment and here...
竟然没有人愿意帮我拉拉链吗?
...offered to do that for me?
真是的
PeopIe.
你穿这么漂亮做什么呢?
So why are you so dressed up?
麦克要来接我去约会
Mike's picking me up for a date.
交往得如何呢? 是不是越来越认真了?
How's that going? Is it getting serious?
我不知道,我不知道 我是蛮喜欢他的
I don't know. I don't know. I mean, I Iike him.
但是我还没有准备好要退出江湖
But am I ready to take my Grade A Ioins off the meat market?
我不太确定
I'm not quite sure.
我真的很欣赏你的约会态度
You know, I reaIIy admire your whoIe dating attitude.
真是很健康的态度 我总是在想会不会进展太快了?…
It's so heaIthy. I'm aIways Iike, ''Is this moving too fast?
会不会进展太慢了? 这将怎么发展呢?
Is this moving too sIow? Where's this going?''
我知道 你就像是个戏剧女王
I know. You are a bit of a drama queen.
你真是太厉害了 男朋友一个接着一个…
You're so much better off. You just go from guy to guy having fun...
享受乐趣,完全不担心没有结局
...and not worrying that it never turns into anything serious.
我不敢说“完全不”
I wouIdn't say ''never.''
有一次有个男的…
You know, there is that guy.
好的,那个…?
Okay, weII, what about...?
总该有个人吧
Okay, there's gotta be someone.
-根本就没有!我就说吧 -喔,天啊,你说的没错!
-There isn't! That's what I'm saying. -Oh, my God, you're right!
我知道,一段恋情才刚结束 马上又可以跟其他人约会
I know. And yet, here you are, aII ready for the next date.
真不敢相信 我之前都没有注意到这点
I can't beIieve I never reaIized this before.
我已经三十几岁了 从来没有爱情长跑过
I'm in my 30s, and I've never been in a Iong-term reIationship.
喔,天啊,我是有什么毛病?
Oh, my God, what's wrong with me?
你没有什么毛病
There's nothing wrong with you.
我是说,你不像那种 看起来会想结婚的人
I mean, you don't strike me as the type of person that wants to get married.
我想结婚!
I want to get married!
别这样,拜…别因为我而哭
No, pIease-- PIease don't cry because of me.
我根本不知道我在说什么 我离婚三次了
I don't know what I'm taIking about, okay? I've been divorced three times.
至少你结过婚
At Ieast you've been married.
喔,我的天啊! 我竟然羡慕起罗斯了?
Oh, my God! I want to trade Iives with Ross?!
菲比
Phoebe.
-怎么了? -没事,要跟你约会太兴奋了
-What's wrong? -Nothing. I'm excited about our date.
麦克,这位是罗斯盖勒 罗斯,这位是麦克…
Mike, this is Ross GeIIer. Ross, this is Mike--
-对不起,我没有听清楚 -麦克汉尼根
-Sorry, I didn't catch that. -Mike Hanigan.
-罗斯盖勒 -嘿
-Ross GeIIer. -Hey.
你确定准备好了吗?
So are you sure you're ready to go?
我看起来怎样?
How do I Iook?
-你皮包里有小镜子吗? -没有
-Do you have a compact in your purse? -No.
你看起来棒透了
You Iook great.
片名:六人行(第九季)
-嘿,乔伊 -那个女的就是不转过来
-Hey, Joey. -This girI won't turn around.
我无法判断她是不是很辣 你觉得呢?
I can't teII if she's hot or not. What do you think?
乔伊,我不会跟你一起把女性物化的
Joey, I am not going to objectify women with you.
但是如果她的脸 跟她的屁股一样棒的话…
But if her face is as nice as her ass....
-妈妈咪啊! -好的,谢谢
-Mama! -AII right. Thanks.
-你有跟钱德讲电话了吗? -他这周末要留在土尔沙
-Have you taIked to ChandIer? -He has to stay in TuIsa this weekend.
-为什么? -我不知道,有工作要做
-How come? -I don't know. He has to work.
要赶那个…
There's some big rush on the....
讨厌!我应该要开始 认真听他讲工作的事了
Damn it. I'm gonna have to start Iistening when he taIks about his job.
你何不飞过去给他个惊喜呢?
Why don't you fIy out there and surprise him?
我很想啊,我真的很想念他
I'd Iove to. I reaIIy miss him.
制片:马克库尼尔斯
But I can't. I have one day off and it's just too expensive.
但是不行,我只有放一天假 而且机票太贵了
真好玩,所以机票钱 比钱德还重要
Interesting. So ChandIer's not worth the price of a pIane ticket to you.
制片:丹娜克莱恩波考
制片:温蒂诺勒
Of course he is.
当然是钱德较重要
或许我应该飞过去
Maybe I wiII go.
编剧:安得鲁瑞奇与泰德哥罕
导演:班怀斯
We'II have a IittIe second honeymoon at the TuIsa Ramada.
我们可以在土尔沙的饭店 来个二度小蜜月
你应该带你那件黑色透明性感内衣 加上吊带裤袜
You shouId bring your bIack see-through teddy with the attached garters.
-你怎么知道我有那件呢? -本来不知道,现在知道了
-How do you know I have one of those? -Didn't untiI just now.
辣,不辣
Hot. Not hot.
辣!
Hot!
什么?
Excuse me?
我说我觉得你很辣
I said that I think you're hot.
而…现在我糗死了
And...now I'm embarrassed.
我以为你是说“嗨”
I thought you said ''hi.''
如果是那样就好了
That wouId've been better.
我来试试看,嗨,我是乔伊
I'II try that. Hi, I'm Joey.
我是海莉
I'm HayIey.
通常我不约在咖啡店遇到的女生出去
Look, I don't normaIIy ask out women that I meet in coffeehouses.
保重
Gesundheit.
但是…
But....
真是很难开口,我有点害羞
This is hard. I'm kind of shy.
真的,你应该去看医生的
SeriousIy, you shouId see someone about that coId.
如果感冒越来越严重,你可是会死的
If it gets much worse, you couId die.
-反正… -我很乐意跟你出去
-Anyway-- -I wouId Iove to go out with you.
真的吗?太棒了
ReaIIy? Great.
我有…我有开口约你吗?
Did I--? Did I actuaIIy ask you?
由你说话的方式 我就猜得到你要做什么
That's just where you were going. I figured I'd heIp you out.
你不像是那种经常这样的男生吧?
You don't seem Iike the kind of guy who does this a Iot?
真是的,阿甘,你传染给我了
Damn it, Gunther, you gave it to me.
喔,是你
Oh, it's you.
我带了素食热狗
With vegetarian corndogs.
别这样,我只想跟你说说话
Come on, I just want to taIk to you.
说什么?说我还剩下几个卵子吗?
About what? How few ova I have Ieft?
别这样,我只想为昨天发生的事道歉
Come on, I just wanna apoIogize for what happened yesterday.
我很抱歉,菲比
I'm sorry, Phoebe.
没关系,罗斯
That's okay, Ross.
-约会还好吗? -糟透了
-So how'd the date go? -WeII, it was awfuI.
我几乎撑不过晚餐
I bareIy got through dinner.
每次我想到你说的话,我就哭了
Every time I thought about what you said, I cried.
我非常肯定他整晚都惊恐的盯着我看
I'm pretty sure he spent most of the night just staring at me in horror.
但是我无法真的确定 因为我的眼睛已经肿到张不开了
But I couIdn't know for sure because my eyes were swoIIen shut.
你知道我不是故意要惹你哭的
You know I wasn't trying to make you cry.
我本来是想要说一些很好听的话的
I was reaIIy trying to say something nice.
我只是要说,即使你 从未有过认真的感情…
I was basicaIIy saying even though you've never been in a serious reIationship--
-我们还要再讨论这个吗? -对不起
-Are we gonna do this again? -Sorry.
-他还没打来吗? -你会打给这种女的吗?
-So he hasn't caIIed? -WouId you caII this girI:
“谢谢…美好…一晚”
''Thanks for...a IoveIy...evening''?
我觉得糟透了 这全都是我的错
Now I feeI terribIe. This is aII my fauIt.
你知道更糟的是什么吗?
You know what you shouId feeI terribIe about?
这男的有可能是可以认真的对象
This couId have been my serious guy.
他很体贴、聪明又风趣
He was sweet and smart and funny.
你知道要遇到这样的男生有多难吗?
You know how hard it is to meet a guy Iike that?
我们的确是稀有动物
We are a rare breed.
嘿,可能就是他哦
Hey, maybe that's him.
喂?
HeIIo?
你可以等一下吗?
CouId you hoId on one sec?
-我需要一点隐私 -是不是麦克呢?
-I need some privacy. -Is it Mike?
不,是骚扰电话 我现在什么都接了
No, it's a heavy breather. I'II take what I can get.
我在线上
I'm Iistening.
晚餐实在太棒了
What a great dinner.
再次谢谢你让我吃最后一块蛋糕
Thanks again for Ietting me have that Iast piece of cake at the restaurant.
不用客气,我要去煮咖啡
You're weIcome again. I'm gonna go make some coffee.
-你要什么呢? -你有蛋糕吗?
-Can I get you anything? -Do you have any cake?
真是进行的太顺利了
So this is going pretty good.
晚餐很棒,我们有许多共同点
Dinner was nice. We've got a lot in common.
“维多莉亚的秘密”性感内衣目录
Victoria's Secret.
我们甚至喜欢相同的书
We even like the same books.
这幅画真可怕
There's a scary painting.
等等
Wait a minute.
我记得好像被这幅画给吓过
I think I've been scared by that painting before.
你知道吗? 这地方看起来真眼熟
You know what? This whole place looks familiar.
我一定曾经来过这里
I have definitely been in this apartment.
我看过这棵可怕的植物
I know I've seen this weird plant before.
它上次也是这样刺我!
It did that the last time!
喔,天啊 我跟这个女的约会过
Oh, my God. I've gone out with this girl before.
没错!我们在这沙发上做过爱!
Yeah! We had sex on this couch!
然后在那张椅子上 还有…,不对
And then on that chair, and-- No.
不对,没有在这里…
No, we didn't do it here...
这倒是很奇怪,看起来超适合的
...which is weird, because it seems like a perfectly good place.
这就是为什么
That's why.
嘿,麦克,很抱歉这样跑过来 我可以进来吗?
Hey, Mike. Sorry to just drop by Iike this. Can I come in?
当然
Sure.
你是谁呢?
Who are you?
我是罗斯,菲比在咖啡屋的朋友
I'm Ross. Phoebe's friend from the coffeehouse?
我真的非常需要跟你谈一件事
I reaIIy, reaIIy need to taIk to you about something.
除非…
UnIess....
你不是要拉我信什么教吧?
You're not gonna try and get me to join a cuIt, are you?
没啦,因为,你知道的 你长得很像那种人
No, it's just, you know, you have that Iook.
该死的199剪发!
Damn Supercuts!
-怎么回事呢?菲比还好吗? -喔,还好,还好
-WeII, what's up? Is Phoebe okay? -Oh, yeah, yeah.
菲比很好,但是…
Phoebe is great. But....
我是个蠢蛋
I'm an idiot, okay?
就在你们出去约会前…
Right before you guys went out...
我不小心惹得她很难过
...I accidentaIIy got her aII upset.
难怪她不对劲
That's why she was weird.
是的,是啊,我…
Yes. Yeah, I....
我说了些蠢话,关于她从没有过 认真的恋爱关系等等
Yeah, I said something stupid about her never having had a serious reIationship.
但是你应该知道,她是很风趣的 很棒的一个人
But you shouId know, she is so much fun. A wonderfuI person.
-拜,别将她判出局 -我不会判她出局的
-PIease, don't bIow her off. -I'm not gonna bIow her off.
我才刚跟她说完电话 我们明晚要出去
I just spoke to her. We're going out tomorrow night.
我是说,如果你没有意见的话 咖啡屋的陌生人
I mean, I hope that's okay with you, stranger from the coffeehouse.
太棒了,所以她狂哭并没有吓跑你?
That's great. So the crying didn't turn you off?
我刚刚跟一个躁郁症患者 结束九年的恋情
I just got out of a nine-year reIationship with a manic-depressive.
跟她相比,菲比根本是只小猫
Compared to that, Phoebe's a Mousketeer.
好吧,那我就不需要再打扰你了
WeII, then, I didn't need to bother you.
你,外加四个麦克汉尼根 都被我打扰了
You or the four other Mike Hanigans I bothered.
其中一个还很高壮 有点爱打情骂俏
One of whom was quite Iarge and a IittIe fIirty.
等等,等等 你刚刚说的是真的吗?
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Is that true what you said?
菲比从未谈过认真的恋爱?
Phoebe's never had a serious reIationship?
她当然有过
Of course she has.
如果她没有谈过认真的恋爱…
If she's never had a serious reIationship...
你认为我会到处去广播…
...do you think I'd go around broadcasting it...
像是无法克制的白痴一样 见人就说吗?
...Iike some kind of unstoppabIe moron?
-但是你的确是那样说了 -是的,是的,我是说了
-But you did say it. -Yes. Yes, I did.
而且我还会说…
And I wiII aIso say...
我接下来要说的…
...what I'm about to say...
相对于…
...vis--vis...
以下的说法
...the foIIowing.
菲比从未谈过认真的恋爱…
Phoebe has never had a serious reIationship...
是从…
...since...
她超级认真地…
...her super-serious reIationship...
跟…
...with...
伟软分手之后
...Vikram.
-伟软? -怎样?那是真的名字
-Vikram? -What? That's a reaI name.
停停吧!
Stop it!
为什么不是派我去德州呢?
Why couIdn't they have sent me to Texas?
七点钟
Seven o'cIock.
或许我该去健身房
Maybe I'II hit the gym.
少来了,还是看情色频道好了
Who am I kidding? Pay-per-view porn.
-不要打扰!不要打扰! -惊喜吧!
-Do not disturb! Do not disturb! -Surprise!
-摩妮卡? -一切都还好吧?
-Monica? -Is everything aII right?
是啊,一切都很好 我刚刚…
Yeah, everything's great. I was just...
在看一些正常的电视节目
...watching some reguIar teIevision there.
这个惊喜真是太令人兴奋了
What a pIeasant surprise.
-我去梳洗一下,好吗? -好的,亲爱的
-I'm gonna go freshen up, okay? -Okay, honey.
差一点点
That was cIose.
-喂 -嘿,瑞秋,是我
-HeIIo. -Hey, Rach, it's me.
我刚到钱德的房间 然后看到他…
Okay, I just got to ChandIer's room, and I caught him...
正在猥亵他自己
...moIesting himseIf.
那画面可能不是很好看
That couIdn't have been pretty.
但是你知道的,男生常那样做的
But you know, guys do that.
但是,很奇怪的是…
WeII, the weird part is...
他在看的是鲨鱼攻击影片耶!
...he was getting off... to a shark-attack show!
-好恶! -是的!钱德竟然在看鲨鱼色情片!
-No! -Yes! ChandIer watches shark porn!
-在看鲨鱼的时候? -是啊
-WhiIe watching sharks? -Yeah.
你确定他是在做那档事吗?
Are you sure that's what he was doing?
你知道我看他 那样跳起来过多少次了吗?
You know how many times I've seen him jump up Iike that?
相信我,我知道他在做什么
BeIieve me, I know what he was doing.
天啊!鲨鱼!
Man! Sharks!
我就知道那个人有地方不对劲
I aIways knew there was something weird about that dude.
你发誓过无论如何都要爱他的
You promised to Iove him no matter what.
“无论如何”讲的是像如果他得病 还是杀了人什么的
''What'' means, Iike, if he gets a disease or kiIIs someone.
而不是如果 他把小弟弟放到鲨鱼嘴里
Not if he gets his joIIies to Jaws.
你知道吗?亲爱的 男生是很不一样的
You know what, honey? Guys are just different.
他们喜欢一些我们无法理解的东西
They Iike things that we can't understand.
我曾经约会过一个男的 总是想要假装…
I once dated this guy who wanted to pretend...
他是考古学家 而我是…
...that he was an archeoIogist, and I was this...
他从冰块中解救出来 调皮的山顶洞女人
...naughty cavewoman who he unfroze from a bIock of ice.
你是在说我哥吗?
Are you taIking about my brother?
我装得不像,对不对?
I didn't disguise that very weII, did I?
-嘿 -嗨
-Hey. -Hi.
我昨晚跟一个女孩子出去 我到一半的时候才发现…
I went out with this girI Iast night. HaIfway through our date I reaIized...
我已经跟她上过床了
...I aIready sIept with her.
所以你已经跟全纽约的女人上过床了 现在只是从头开始再来一次?
You've sIept with aII the women in N.Y., and now you're going around again?
这还不是最奇怪的地方
That's not even the weird part.
-她竟然不记得跟我上过床了! -你也不记得跟她上过床啊
-She didn't remember sIeeping with me! -You don't remember sIeeping with her.
但是她应该要记得的 我可是很令人难忘的!
But she shouId remember sIeeping with me. I am very memorabIe!
-你们知道的 -我们怎么会知道呢?
-You guys know. -How do we know?
-我们又没有跟你上过床 -那是谁的错呢?
-We've never sIept with you. -And whose fauIt is that?
又没有什么大不了的 你忘了,她忘了
What's the big deaI? You forgot, she forgot.
-或许那天晚上你没有达阵! -嘿!
-Maybe you were having an off night. -Hey!
我向来都有达阵的,好吗?
I never have an off night. Okay?
虽然有时候如果我吃太胀 可能就不会觉得很性感
AIthough, sometimes if I'm a IittIe bIoated, I don't feeI that sexy.
但是即使是那样,我都比别人强!
But even then, I'm better than most!
亲爱的,你何不就此释怀 再约她出去呢?
Honey, why don't you just Iet it go and ask her out again?
你们都是骚货 你们根本都不记得跟谁上过床
You're both so sIutty, you don't remember who you sIept with.
你们是天生的一对
You're made for each other.
真有趣
Interesting.
好吧,我会再跟她出去 然后忘了过去
WeII, I'II go out with her again and I'II try to get past it.
不吃盐!会胀气!
No saIt! BIoaty!
-乔伊? -干嘛?
-Joey? -What?
你会觉得鲨鱼很性感吗?
You don't think sharks are sexy, do you?
不会
No.
等一下,等等 小美人鱼是鲨鱼吗?
Wait a minute. Wait, what was the LittIe Mermaid?
门没锁!
It's open!
-嘿 -麦克打电话来了,我们要再约会了!
-Hey. -Mike caIIed! We're going out again!
一件小事,我去找麦克谈过
Quick thing. I went to taIk to Mike.
什么?
What?
你做…? 你做了什么?罗斯
What did you--? What did you do, Ross?
喔,天啊,光这样你就生气了
Oh, boy. You got mad at that part.
我过去找他,告诉他…
I went over there, you know, to teII him how....
你是个很棒的人,但是…
How great you are. But....
嗯,你知道我的,话太多了
WeII, you know me. BIah-bIah-bIah.
-然后我最后竟然告诉他… -什么?
-And I ended up teIIing him that.... -What?
你有过六年的恋情…
You had a six-year-Iong reIationship...
跟一个叫做伟软的人
...with a guy named Vikram.
什么?为什么?
What? Why?
因为,他…
WeII, he seemed...
在我说你从未谈过 认真的恋情之后,好像有点惊讶
...to bum hard when I toId him you'd never been in a serious reIationship.
如果你不是刚跟我 最要好的朋友生下小孩
If you hadn't just had a baby with my best friend...
我跟撒旦发誓…
...I swear to Lucifer...
一只狂犬病疯狗正要吃掉 你裤档里的那根东西了!
...a rabid dog wouId be feasting on your dangIers right now!
我想如果你知道多一点关于伟软的事…
I think you'II feeI differentIy when you know...
你会感觉好多了
...a IittIe bit about Vikram.
好的,他是…
Okay, he's a....
他是风筝设计师
He's a kite designer.
而且他曾经跟于美人约会过
And he used to date Oprah.
我不会跟你唱双簧说谎的,罗斯
I'm not going aIong with some Iie you made up, Ross.
-我会跟他老实说 -很好
-I'm just gonna be honest with him. -Good.
跟他老实说
Just be honest with him.
-我没有什么好隐瞒的 -没错
-I have nothing to be ashamed of. -No.
就算我的每段感情 没都有超过一个月…
So I haven't been in a reIationship that Iasted Ionger than a month.
那又如何呢?是啊 我是没有过真正的男朋友
Okay? I haven't had a reaI boyfriend.
如果他无法接受 那他可以离开,我想他会离开的
If he can't handIe it, then he can Ieave. Which he wiII.
而这一切都没有关系 我只不过会永远孤单而已
And, you know, that's okay. So I'II just be aIone forever.
都没关系了,一切都会没事的
You know, aII right. It'II be fine. It'II be fine.
我就跟寡妇还有同性恋一起出去玩嘛
I'II go on waIking tours with widows and Iesbians.
-我去开门 -好的
-I'II get it. -Okay.
让我想想有哪一次,开门的人不是你
I'm trying to remember the Iast time I opened a door and you weren't there.
菲比,你还好吗?
Phoebe, are you okay?
还好,只不过是…
Yeah. There's just....
有件事你必须要知道
There's something you shouId know.
伟软刚打电话来
Vikram just caIIed.
所以在经历二十五年的婚姻之后 这真是很让人惊讶
So it was reaIIy a shock after 25 years of marriage...
我的模范父母竟然要离婚 我真的很难接受
...my parents getting divorced. I took it the hardest...
-因为我是老么 -当然
-...because I was the youngest. -Sure. Yeah.
你怎么会忘了我是谁?
How can you not remember me?
什么?
What?
你怎么会忘了我们上过床?
How couId you not remember that we sIept together?
-什么?何时? -我不知道!
-What? When? -I don't know!
我真的、真的认为 如果有我会记得的
I reaIIy, reaIIy think I wouId remember sIeeping with you.
快点,快点 仔细回想,好吗?那就在…
Come on, come on. Search your brain, aII right? It was...
之前某个时候 我在这里,你在这里
...a certain amount of time ago. I was here. You were here.
我们在这里,这里,这里…
We had sex here, here, here....
没有那里,嘿咻
Not there.
-想起来了吗? -没,一点印象也没有
-Anything? -No, it's not ringing any beIIs.
天啊,女人!
My God, woman!
你跟多少人上过床 让你根本不记得我?
How many peopIe have you been with not to remember this?
嘿,海莉 我们真的要修理那个门把了
Hey, HayIey. We reaIIy gotta fix that doorknob.
乔伊?
Joey?
我跟你上过床!
I sIept with you!
而且很明显的你记得我! 嘿,表示我还不赖!
And you obviousIy remember me! Hey, I stiII got it!
所以我们还好嘛
So we're good.
我自己出去
I'II Iet myseIf out.
然后我说,伟软…
And I said, ''Okay, Vikram...
你不能每次寂寞就打电话给我
...you can't just caII every time you get IoneIy.
在你跟瑞秋上床之后 你就没有那个权力了
You gave up that right when you sIept with RacheI.''
瑞秋?我以为她才刚生下罗斯的小孩
RacheI? I thought she just had a baby with Ross.
是啊,嗯…
Yeah, weII....
是啊
Yeah.
艾玛的出生证明上或许生父是罗斯…
But Emma's birth certificate might say ''GeIIer'' ...
但是她长得像伟软
...but her eyes say ''Mukherjee.''
这实在太糟了 而且他还吸强力胶?
That is so wrong. And on top of that, he's a gIue sniffer?
我知道,但是他打来时 我的心就飞向他了
I know. But he caIIs, and my heart goes to him.
你知道的,那个浑蛋是个很会 说话的风筝设计师
You know, that bastard is one smooth-taIking freeIance kite designer.
如果你要的话,我可以帮你修理他
If you want, I'II mess him up for you.
真的吗?
You wouId do that?
除非他很大只 如果他真的很大只,我会给他…
UnIess he's big. If he's reaIIy big, I'II send him...
一封信,骂死他
...a rude Ietter.
我想有更好的人在等着你
I think there's somebody better out there for you.
我是说,你知道的,我… 我不是指我,但是…
I mean, you know, I'm-- I'm not saying me, but....
或许…是我
Maybe...me.
而且你不用担心我会吸强力胶
And you don't have to worry about gIue-sniffing with me.
虽然有时候我会闻麦克笔的味道
AIthough, I do smeII the occasionaI Magic Marker.
是啊,反正,我只是…
Yeah. Anyway, I just....
我想我可以让你快乐
I think I can make you happy.
-好了,我办不到 -怎么了?
-Okay, I can't do this. -What's wrong?
根本没有伟软这个人 罗斯乱扯的
WeII, there is no Vikram. Ross made him up.
因为我…
Because I....
我从未有过爱情长跑
I reaIIy never have been in a Iong-term reIationship.
我从未跟男人同居过 从来没有庆祝交往一周年
I've never Iived with a guy. I've never even ceIebrated an anniversary.
所以…
So....
如果这对你而言太奇怪…
If that's too weird for you...
所以你想现在就走人 我可以理解
...and you want to Ieave, I understand.
事实上,我要闭上双眼 让这一切不至于太尴尬
In fact, I'II cIose my eyes to make it Iess awkward.
你亲了我
You kissed me.
-你不认为我是怪人吗? -不
-You don't think I'm a totaI freak? -No.
那么…
WeII....
那,我可不…?
Look, can I...?
我可不可以认为你有点怪 但又有点酷…
Can I think you're a IittIe weird and aIso cooI...
因为你告诉我事情的真相 而且让我想亲你?
...for teIIing me the truth and aIso want to kiss you?
我想应该可以
I guess so.
我可不可以认为,你亲我真是很酷…
Can I think it's cooI that you kissed me...
而且我想要亲回去?
...and aIso want to kiss you again?
有一点担心奇异笔的事可以吗?
And be a IittIe concerned about the Magic Markers?
当然可
DefiniteIy.
我是伟软
This is Vikram.
我需要跟你谈我们之间 那段长期的恋情
I need to talk to you about the long-term relationship we had.
回电给我,我在我的风筝工作室
Call me. I am in my kite-making studio.
嗨,亲爱的,我回来了
Hi, honey, I'm home.
嗨
Hi.
-旅途还好吗? -不错
-How was your fIight? -It was great.
我从飞机上的购物目录订了浮板
I ordered a pooI fIoat from the Sky MaII.
为什么我要订呢?
Why'd I do that?
过来坐下吧
Why don't you sit down.
放轻松、舒服点
Get yourseIf comfortabIe.
因为我有个小…
Because I have a IittIe...
惊喜要给你
...surprise for you.
喔,喔,喔 土尔沙现在一定是五点…
WeII, weII, weII. It must be 5:00 in TuIsa...
因为纽约现在是“六”点(音近性)!
...because it's ''sex o'cIock'' in N.Y.C.!
好了,这代表我有多爱你
Okay. This is how much I Iove you.
大白鲨…
The great white....
亲爱的?
Honey?
为什么要我看一群鲨鱼游来游去呢?
Why am I watching a bunch of sharks swimming around?
这不是…? 这不是你爱看的吗?
Is this--? Is this not the good part?
要我快转吗? 转到露齿…比较多的地方吗?
Do you want me to fast-forward to something...toothier?
不,我只是想确定 你是不是拿错了录影带
No, I'm just not sure that you got the right movie, that's aII.
录影带店里只有这一卷
This is the onIy one they had at our video store.
不过他们倒是有一部叫“鳄鱼杀手”的
Though they did have something caIIed Crocodile Killers.
还是说,你非要鲨鱼不可呢?
Or does it aIways have to be sharks?
为什么我非要鲨鱼不可?
Does what aIways have to be sharks?
听着,我们可以来点别的
Look, we can do something eIse.
你要我到浴缸里…再用力扭吗?
Do you want me to get into the tub and...thrash?
-到底是怎么回事? -没关系,没关系的
-What's going on? -It's okay. It's okay.
我还是爱你的
I stiII Iove you.
-让我了解这一切 -是你应该让我了解这一切!
-Let me be a part of this. -Let me be a part of this!
我看到你在土尔沙做的事
I saw what you were doing in TuIsa.
愤怒的鲨鱼让你“性”奋!
Angry sharks turn you on!
不,并没有
No, they don't.
那为什么你一边看着们 一边自己玩呢?
Then why were you watching them and giving yourseIf a treat?
喔,天啊!当你一进来 我就转台了
Oh, my God! When you came in, I switched the channeI.
我本来只是在看一般的色情片
I was just watching reguIar porn.
真的吗?
ReaIIy?
是的,只不过是一些正常 老套、美式的女对女动作片
Yes. Just some good, oId-fashioned, American, girI-on-girI action.
这件事真是让我太高兴了
Can I teII you how happy that makes me?
你是个不可思议的老婆
You are an amazing wife.
真的,太不可思议了 你真的愿意为我这样做?
ReaIIy, you are amazing. You were actuaIIy gonna do this for me?
你是怎么会有这样的 意志跟谅解呢?
Where do you find the strength and the understanding for that?
因为我现在非常、非常地醉
I'm very, very drunk right now.
通常我会去跟她搭讪的 但是我的自信已经动摇了
OrdinariIy, I wouId taIk to her, but my confidence is shaken.
我有跟她上床吗? 我没有跟她上床吗?
Did I sIeep with her? Did I not sIeep with her?
或许该是你反省的时候了 检讨你的整个约会态度
Maybe this is a wake-up caII. You know, about your whoIe dating attitude.
你已经三十好几了 没有谈过一个长期的恋爱
You're in your 30s and you have never been in a Iong-term reIationship.
女人从一个换到另一个…
Here you go from woman to woman...
没有意义的关系 换到另一个没有意义的关系
...meaningIess experience to meaningIess experience.
从不担心这些恋情都没有任何的发展
Never even worrying that it doesn't turn into something more serious.
你说的没错,我爱死我的人生了!
You're right. I Iove my Iife!
事实上我跟她上过床了
I actuaIIy did sIeep with her.